So, let's look at a formal version of Bayes Theorem.
下面 我们看一下贝叶斯定理的正式表达
Initially, we start with an event,
首先要有一个事件
and this event could be A or B.
这个事件可以是 A 或 B
The probabilities for each are here,
二者的概率分别表示为
P of A and P of B.
P(A) 以及 P(B)
Now we observe a third event,
现在又有了第三个事件
and that event can either happen, or not happen,
在 A 和 B 事件的条件下 这第三个事件可能发生 也可能不发生
both for A and for B. R is going to help us
通过以下方式
find more exact probabilities for A and B in the following way.
R 能够帮助我们更精确地确定事件 A 和 B 的概率
Let's say we can calculate the probability of our given A,
我们能计算事件 A 的条件下 R 的概率 P(R|A)
and also of R complement,
以及 A 的条件下 R 的互补事件的概率
which is not R given A.
就是说在 A 的条件下 R 事件不发生的概率
And similarly for R given B,
同样 在 B 的条件下 R 事件的概率 P(R|B)
and R complement given B.
以及在 B 的条件下 R 的互补事件的概率
Now, our set of scenarios are these four,
我们已知的情况共有这四种
R n A, R complement n A,
R∩A R 的互补事件 ∩A
R n B, and R complement and B.
R∩B R 的互补事件 ∩B
But since we know R occurred,
我们知道事件 R 已经发生了
then we know that the second and the fourth events are not possible.
所以第二种和第四种情况不符合条件
So our new universe consists of the two events,
只剩两种情况
R n A and R n B.
R∩A 和 R∩B
We calculate the probability for A n R,
我们计算一下 A∩R 的概率
or equivalently A intersection R. And by the Law of Conditional Probability,
也就是事件 A 和 事件 R 的交集 根据条件概率
this is P F A times B of R given A.
应是 P（A） 乘 P(R|A)
Similarly, for B intersection R. And now since these probabilities do not add to one,
同样的方法计算事件 B 和 R 的交集 因为这两个概率相加不等于一
we just divide them both by their sum,
所以我们让它们分别除以二者的和
so that the new normalized probabilities now do add to one.
新得到的归一化概率相加即等于一
Thus, we get the following formulas for P of A given R and P of B given R.
因此 我们用下面的公式来计算 P(A|R) 和 P(B|R)
These are our new and improved probabilities for A and B after we know that R occured.
这是在已知 R 事件发生后 新得到的事件 A 和 B 的概率
Again, B of A and P of B are called the prior probabilities,
总之 P(A) 和 P(B) 被称为先验概率
which is what we knew before we knew that R occurred.
是我们在不知道 R 事件发生的情况下 计算得到的事件 A 和 B 的概率
P of A given R and P of B given R are posterior probabilities,
P(A|R) 和 P(B|R) 被称作后验概率
which is what we inferred after we knew that R occurred.
是我们在已知 R 事件发生的情况下 推断出的 A 和 B 事件的概率
And here it is, the formula for Bayes Theorem.
这就是贝叶斯定理